boredlion.com 2018-01-31

# Privacy Policy - BoredLion.com

* * *

**Introduction**  
This Privacy Policy describes how BoredLion.com is doing business as BoredLion.com. BoredLion.com collects and uses non-personally identifying information from users of the BoredLion.com website at http://www.BoredLion.com along with all subdomains, collectively, the Site.

We never knowingly collect or maintain information at or on our Site from those we actually know are under 18 years old, and no part of our Site is directed at or structured to attract anyone under 18 years old. Visitors younger than 18 years of age may NOT use the Site and must LEAVE immediately.

 **How we Collect and Use Non-Personally Identifying Information**  
As is true of most Web sites, we gather Web server log file information automatically such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. We use this information to administer our Site, understand how visitors navigate through our Site and to enhance your experience while using our Site.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Cookies and web beacons are very small text files that are stored on your computer when you visit certain web pages. BoredLion.com collects information through cookies and web beacons about your web browsing activities such as the address of the page you are visiting, the address of the referrer page you previously visited, the time you are viewing the page, your browsing environment and your display settings. We use cookies and web beacons on our Site to:

Understand traffic patterns and the number of visitors to the Site and other non-BoredLion.com websites that we partner with;  
Understand how you use and interact with the Site;  
Improve the BoredLion.com products and services;  
Optimize your experience on our Site;  
Provide anonymous individual or aggregate auditing, research, modeling and reporting for our advertisers and other partners (no personally identifiable information about you is shared with our advertisers and other partners as part of these activities);  
Provide you relevant advertising and content; and  
Properly manage our Site.

Please note that some cookies may be placed by a third party service provider who performs some of these functions for us. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.

If you are concerned about cookies, most browsers permit individuals to decline cookies. A user refusing cookies can still fully navigate our Site.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

 **Links to Other Web Sites**  
This Site may contain links to other sites owned by third parties. Your use of each of those sites is at your own risk and is subject to the terms of those sites. BoredLion.com has no control over sites that are not ours, and BoredLion.com is not responsible for any changes to or content on them. BoredLion.com assumes no responsibility for the content of or services offered by linked third-party sites, and makes no representations regarding the accuracy of materials on third-party Web sites. Statements made on third-party Web sites linked to or from this Site reflect only the views of their authors and not of BoredLion.com. BoredLion.com’s inclusion on the Site of any third-party content or a link to a third-party site is not an endorsement of that content or third-party site.

 **Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
BoredLion.com reserves the right to update and change, from time to time, this Privacy Policy and all documents incorporated by reference. You can find the most recent version of this Privacy Policy at http://www.BoredLion.com/privacy/. If BoredLion.com changes this Privacy Policy in ways that affect whether and how it uses your personally identifying information, BoredLion.com will advise you of choices you may have as a result of those changes. BoredLion.com will also post a notice on its home page that this Privacy Policy has changed. Use of the Site after such changes constitutes acceptance of such changes.

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or want to contact us, please send an email to **boredlion@gmail.com**.
